{
  "extraDescription": "each operand is in 0-5",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "1 &times; 2",
      "answer": "2"
    },
    {
      "question": "5 &times; 2",
      "answer": "10"
    },
    {
      "question": "0 &times; 3",
      "answer": "0"
    },
    {
      "question": "0 &times; 1",
      "answer": "0"
    },
    {
      "question": "0 &times; 5",
      "answer": "0"
    },
    {
      "question": "5 &times; 1",
      "answer": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "0 &times; 0",
      "answer": "0"
    },
    {
      "question": "2 &times; 2",
      "answer": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "4 &times; 2",
      "answer": "8"
    },
    {
      "question": "1 &times; 3",
      "answer": "3"
    },
    {
      "question": "2 &times; 0",
      "answer": "0"
    },
    {
      "question": "3 &times; 5",
      "answer": "15"
    },
    {
      "question": "4 &times; 3",
      "answer": "12"
    },
    {
      "question": "1 &times; 0",
      "answer": "0"
    },
    {
      "question": "2 &times; 1",
      "answer": "2"
    },
    {
      "question": "3 &times; 3",
      "answer": "9"
    },
    {
      "question": "2 &times; 4",
      "answer": "8"
    },
    {
      "question": "4 &times; 0",
      "answer": "0"
    },
    {
      "question": "3 &times; 2",
      "answer": "6"
    },
    {
      "question": "1 &times; 1",
      "answer": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "0 &times; 2",
      "answer": "0"
    },
    {
      "question": "5 &times; 3",
      "answer": "15"
    },
    {
      "question": "2 &times; 3",
      "answer": "6"
    },
    {
      "question": "3 &times; 4",
      "answer": "12"
    },
    {
      "question": "0 &times; 4",
      "answer": "0"
    },
    {
      "question": "1 &times; 5",
      "answer": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "5 &times; 5",
      "answer": "25"
    },
    {
      "question": "4 &times; 1",
      "answer": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "2 &times; 5",
      "answer": "10"
    },
    {
      "question": "3 &times; 1",
      "answer": "3"
    },
    {
      "question": "1 &times; 4",
      "answer": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "4 &times; 5",
      "answer": "20"
    },
    {
      "question": "5 &times; 0",
      "answer": "0"
    },
    {
      "question": "3 &times; 0",
      "answer": "0"
    },
    {
      "question": "5 &times; 4",
      "answer": "20"
    },
    {
      "question": "4 &times; 4",
      "answer": "16"
    }
  ]
}
